Ross kissed me. No! Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God! It's unbelievable! Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God!
Okay, alright, we want to hear everything. Monica, get the wine and unplug the phone. Okay.
Rachel, does this end well or do we need to get tissues? Oh, it ended very well.
Oh, do not start without me! Do not start without me!
Okay, alright, let's hear about the kiss. Was it like, was it like a soft brush against your lips or was it like a, you know, I gotta have you now kind of thing?
Well, at first it was really intense, you know, and then, oh God, and then we just sort of sunk into it.
Oh, so, okay, was he holding you or was his hands like on your back?
No, actually, first they, they were, they started out on my waist and then they slid up and then they were in my hair. Oh!
And, uh, and then I kissed her. Tongue? Yeah. Cool.
So, no one told you life was gonna be this way. Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's the old way.
It's like you're always stuck in second gear. When it hasn't been your day, week, month, even your year.
But I'll be there for you. When it starts to pour. I'll be there for you. Like I've been there before. I'll be there for you.
All right, check out this bad boy. 12 megabytes of RAM, 500 megabyte hard drive, built-in spreadsheet capabilities, and a modem that transmits at over 28,000 BPS.
Wow. What are you gonna use it for? Games and stuff.
There are no jobs. There are no jobs for me.
Oh, wait, here's one. Uh, would you be willing to cook naked?
There's an app for a naked chef? No, but if you're willing to cook naked, then you might be willing to dance naked. There you go.
Hi. Hey. Hey. Oh, so, um, how'd you make out last night?
That is funny. That is painfully funny. No, wait, wait. Yeah, that's just painful.
Wait a minute. I thought last night was great. Yeah, it was, but I get home, okay, and I see Julie's saline solution on my night table.
And I'm thinking to myself, oh, my God, what the hell am I doing? I mean, here I am. I'm with Julie, this incredible great woman who I care about and who cares about me.
And I'm like, what, am I just gonna throw all that away? You got all that from saline solution?
I'm the same way. Show me a bottle of Visine, and I'm like, whoa, who am I?
Wait a minute. We're talking about Rachel here. You and Rachel. Believe me, I've been dreaming about me and Rachel for like ten years now.
But now I'm with Julie. You know, so it's like me and Julie, me and Rachel, me and Julie, me and Rachel, Rachel, Rachel.
Hey, you. How are you? Good. How are you? Good. Hi, honey. Hi, Julie. Hi, Julie. Julie.
Um, how are you? Good. Good. So everybody's here. Everybody's good. Good and great in here.
So were you gonna play something, Phoebe? Well, actually, I did. Play it.
All right. Hey, Julie, I didn't know you wore lenses. What?
Okay. Um, hi. Hello. Hi. Okay. So, um, this is a song about a love triangle between three people that I made up.
Um, it's called, um, Two of Them Kissed Last Night.
There was a girl we'll call her Betty, and a guy, let's call him Neil.
Now, I can't stress this point too strongly, this story isn't real.
Now, our Neil must decide who will be the girl that he casts aside.
Will Betty be the one who he loves truly, or will it be the one who we'll call Lululee?
He must decide. He must decide. Even though I made him up, he must decide.
Well, this is a nice resume. Nice, nice, nice. Muy empresivo.
Shame none of it's true. I'm kidding. I'm kidding. No, it's all true. I'm just a little nervous, that's all.
I'm fine now. So, Mr. Rastetter, what exactly does this job entail? The ad wasn't too clear.
Mock-a-lit. I'm sorry? Mock-a-lit. It's a completely synthetic chocolate substitute.
Ooh. Well, go ahead, try a piece. Yeah, we think that mock-a-lit is even better than chocolate.
All right. Mm-hmm.
Mmm. Yeah? I love how it crumbles.
See, chocolate doesn't do that. No, ma'am.
Well, anywho, we should be getting our FDA approval any day now. Hopefully in time for Thanksgiving.
See, the way we look at it, chocolate already dominates most of your major food preparation holidays, Easter, Christmas, what have you.
Mm-hmm. But we're thinking, given the right marketing, we can make Thanksgiving the mock-a-lit holiday.
Wow. You going to swallow that?
It's waiting for it to stop bubbling. Yeah, isn't that great?
Well, anywho, we're looking for a couple of chefs who can create some Thanksgiving-themed recipes.
You think you might be interested? Absolutely.
Absolutely. See, I love creating new recipes, I love Thanksgiving, and well, now, I love mock-a-lit.
Really? Mmm. Especially that aftertaste, you know. I tell you, that'll last you until Christmas.
How about mock-a-lit mousse? It's not very Thanksgiving-y.
How about pilgrim mock-a-lit mousse? What makes it pilgrim? We'll put buckles on it.
Hey. Hey. Hey. Did Ross call? No, I'm sorry.
Why didn't he call? He's going to stay with Julie, isn't he? He's going to stay with her, and she's going to be all,
Hi, I'm Julie. Ross picked me. And we're going to get married and have lots of kids and dig up stuff together.
No offense, but that sounds nothing like her.
I don't know what I'm going to do. What am I going to do? I mean, this is like a complete nightmare.
Oh, I know. This must be so hard. Oh, no. Two women love me.
They're both gorgeous and sexy. My wall is too small for my fifties, and my diamond shoes are too tight.
Hey, here's a thought, Ross. Don't touch a computer. Don't ever touch a computer.
Ross, listen. I got two words for you. Threesome.
Still have another word if you want to use that.
Oh, hey. I think I know what it is. Help.
Okay. All right. Look, let's get logical about this, okay? We'll make a list. Rachel and Julie, pros and cons.
Oh. Okay.
We'll put their names in bold with different fonts, and I can use different colors for each column.
Can't we just use a pen? No, Amish boy.
All right. Let's start with the cons, because they're more fun. Rachel first.
I don't know. I mean, all right. I guess you can say she's a little spoiled sometimes.
You could say that.
I guess, you know, sometimes she's a little ditzy, you know?
And I've seen her be a little too into her looks.
Oh, and like, Julie and I, we have a lot in common because we're both paleontologists, right?
But, I mean, Rachel's just a waitress.
Waitress. Got it. You guys want to play Doom?
Or we could keep doing this.
What else?
I don't know.
Oh, her ankles are a little chubby.
Okay, let's do Julie. What's wrong with her?
She's not Rachel.
Okay, this is pumpkin pie with a mocklet cookie crumb crust.
This is mocklet cranberry cake, and these are mocklet chip cookies.
Just like the Indians served.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, good?
Oh, my God, I can't believe you let me put this in my mouth.
Oh, oh, wait. Lord, oh, this is what evil must taste like.
I'm telling you, this thing won't print.
Yes, I pressed that button like a hundred times.
You know, for a hotline, you're not so hot.
What is that in the background?
Are you watching Star Trek?
Hey, so how'd it go with Julie? Did you break her heart?
Yes. It was horrible. She cried. I cried.
She threw things. They hit me.
Anyway, I did the right thing.
So, Spock actually hugs his father?
Hey, do you guys have...
Hi.
Where are you going?
I, uh, I just got back from, uh, from Julie's.
Oh.
No, no, it's not what you think. It's, um, it's the other thing.
Well, uh...
He broke up with Julie.
Well, go hug her, for God's sakes.
Really?
Really. It's always been you, Rach.
Oh, God.
Oh.
Oh, this is good. This is really good.
I know. I know. It's, it's almost...
What do you say we go take a walk? Just us, not them?
Let me get my coat.
Okay. No, hey, whoa, whoa. I'll get your coat.
Okay.
Whoop!
He's going to get my coat.
He's going to get my coat! Oh, my God!
You guys, I can't believe it! This is unbelievable!
What's that?
What? Nothing.
What? I thought I saw my name. What is it?
No, no. See? See?
Hey, it's printing!
Well, what is it? Let me see.
Hey. Hey, someone order a coat?
Ross, Chandler wrote something about me on his computer, and he won't let me see.
He won't? He won't?
Because isn't that, isn't that the, the, the short story you were writing?
Yes, yes, it is the short story that I was writing.
In a minute? Well, let me read it.
No!
Come on!
Hey, uh, why don't you read it to her?
All right.
It was summer,
and it was hot.
Rachel was there.
A lonely gray couch.
Oh, look, cried Ned.
And then the kingdom was his forever, the end.
That's it? That's all you wrote?
You're the worst writer in the whole world!
All right, all right. You know what? This isn't funny anymore.
There's something about me on that piece of paper, and I want to see it.
No, you don't.
You know what? Fine. If you guys want to be children about this, that's fine.
I do not need to see it.
Ah!
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
What is this?
That is, um...
That's, that's...
Ross, what is this?
Thank you. Good luck.
Okay, just, just remember how crazy I am about you, okay?
Kind of ditzy?
Too into her looks?
Spoiled?
Now, that's a little spoiled.
He was supposed to type little, the idiot.
Just a waitress?
Now, that, that was, uh...
I mean, as opposed to, uh...
The, um...
Okay, is, is this over yet?
Rach?
I do not have chubby ankles!
No, I...
No, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Okay, okay, look at the other side.
Look at Julie's column.
She's not Racham?
What the hell's a Racham?
Is that some stupid paleontology word that I wouldn't know
because I'm just a waitress?
Rach, come on, Rach!
Rach!
Rach, no, no, no, it's, it's...
She's not Rachel.
She's, she's not...
Ra...
Rachel.
My diary.
My diary, that's brilliant.
I should have told her it was my diary.
She never would have made me read her my diary.
No, that's true.
You know, you'd be a great person to have around the day
after an emergency.
I, I cannot believe Ross even made this list.
I know.
What a dinkus.
Hey, cut him some slack.
It was Chandler's idea.
What?
Oh, good, I was hoping that would come up.
This was your idea?
All right, let, let's get some perspective here, okay?
These things, they happen for a reason.
Yeah, you!
All right, Pheebs, back me up here, okay?
You believe in that karma crap, don't you?
Listen, by the way,
good luck in your next life as a dung beetle.
Rich!
Hey, open up, please.
When somebody does not buzz you in, Ross,
that means go away.
That doesn't mean please climb up the fire escape.
Yeah, I just wanted to read you something.
It's your pro list.
Not interested.
Okay, okay, number one,
the way you cry at game shows.
Number two,
how much you love your friends.
Number three,
the way you play with your hair when you're nervous.
Number four,
how brave you are for starting a life over.
Number five,
how great you are with Ben.
Number six,
the way you smell.
Hey, Ross, what are you doing?
Hey, Joe, you want to open the window?
Oh, yeah, we...
What are you doing out there?
I, I, um...
Oh, my gosh, you must be freezing.
You know what you need?
How about a nice steaming cup of hot mocklet?
Reg, come on, open up.
Reg, come on, come on.
You gotta give me another chance.
No.
No?
That's what I said.
Look, maybe we should go.
No, you guys, you really don't have to go.
We're done talking.
Reg, come on, look, I know how you must feel.
No, you don't, Ross.
Imagine the worst things you think about yourself.
Now, how would you feel if the one person
that you trusted the most in the world
not only thinks them, too,
but actually uses them
as reasons not to be with you?
No, but, but...
See, I want to be with you
in spite of all those things.
Oh, well, that's, that's mighty big of you, Ross.
I said don't go!
You know what?
If, if things were the other way around,
there is nothing you could put on the list
that would, that would ever make me not want to be with you.
Well, then I guess that's the difference between us.
See, I'd never make a list.
I never know how long you're supposed to wait
in this type of situation
before you can talk again, you know?
Maybe a little longer.
Now, in some of these recipes,
the quantities may seem just a little unusual.
Uh, like these coconut mocklet holiday nut bars.
I've indicated four cups of coconut
and four cups of crushed nut
and only, uh, one tablespoon of mocklet.
Doesn't matter.
What?
Our FDA approval didn't come through.
Something about laboratory rats.
Oh, gosh, I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Well, anywho, here's your check.
Thank you for all the trouble you went through.
Um, listen, you didn't, uh,
eat a lot of it while you were cooking, did you?
Well, I ate some.
Oh, some. That's fine. Some is fine.
Some is not a lot.
Okay.
So it doesn't burn when you pee, does it?
Hello?
Hi.
Is that him again?
Tell him I'd come to the phone,
but my ankles are weighing me down.
Listen, I-I don't think this is the best time.
Look, can... can you do something for me?
Sure, what?
Okay.
I'll be right back.
All right.
Music!
The next one's dedicated to Rachel from Ross.
Rachel, he wants you to know he's deeply sorry for what he did,
and he hopes you can find it in your heart to forgive him.
See the stone set in your eyes
See the phone twist in your side
I'll wait for you
Sleight of hand and twist of faith
On a bed of nails she makes me waste
And I'll wait without you
Uh, we've just gotten a call from Rachel
and she told us what Ross did.
It's pretty appalling.
And, Ross, if you're listening,
I don't want to play your song anymore.
Why don't we devote our time to a couple that stands a chance?
Avery, Michelle, sorry she hit you with her car,
and she hopes you two will work it out.
There's a room where I can go
And tell my secrets too
In my room
Hi. Thanks for coming in again.
Oh, not at all. I have no morals and I need the cash.
It's like I'm looking in a mirror.
Anyway, they're called pistachios.
Now, they taste exactly like pistachios,
but they're made primarily of reconstituted fish bits.
Here, try one.
All right.
You're not allergic to anything, are you?
Cat hair.
Oh, sorry.